{
  "openingRemarks": "an operand of at most 5 and an operand between 6 and 9",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + 2\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 9\\)",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 3\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 4\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 + 7\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + 8\\)",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 5\\)",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 + 6\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 0\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 + 1\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    }
  ]
}
